ucanapply.com 2018-08-25

# Privacy-Ucanapply

**Effective Date : From 1st of January, 2011 onwards**  
UCanApply.com's Apply Online Program, hosted through ucanapply.com, is an Internet property of Learning Spiral Pvt Ltd. ("UCanApply.com," "we," "our," or "us"). This UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy is given by Learning Spiral Pvt. Ltd and is applicable to users of the Apply Online Program (the "Apply Online Program" applies to all services performed by UCanApply.com on behalf of the colleges, schools, educational boards, exam conducting bodies and/or universities to include the hosting of online application forms, inquiry forms, event forms and interview forms) for applications made to colleges, schools, educational boards, exam conducting bodies and/or universities (in short "schools"). We are providing this UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy to you so that you can learn about how we collect and share information you submit through the Apply Online Program. Data privacy and security is important to us and to users of the Apply Online Program, so we want to make sure that users of our Apply Online Program understand our privacy and security practices and policies. In addition to this UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy, we are fully committed to adhering to all relevant rules, regulations, laws as prevailing in India relevant to our services.  
This UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy will tell you the following:  

  * What information we collect/track about you.
  * With whom we share the information we collect/track.
  * How we use the information we collect/track.

This UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy applies to the information you provide to us through the Apply Online Program. 

#### Information Collection Practices and Policies

UCanApply.com's Apply Online Program allows you to apply to schools, colleges, educational boards, exam conducting bodies and Universities you select. Each school requires you to provide the information requested on its application. In order for your application to be processed, all information requested by a school must be provided. In connection with processing your application, we may collect payment or billing information (e.g., credit card information) from you to pay the school's application fees. When you apply to a school using our Apply Online Program, we share the information you provide with the school. The information you may be requested to submit may include (but is not limited to): (1) Name, (2) Address, (3) Email Address, (4) Telephone Number, (5) Domicile, and (6) Date of Birth (7) Category, (8) Class, (9) Gender etc.  
We use the following services to monitor the processing of your application: Web analytics and Web hosting. We use a credit card payment processing service provider to process any payments required to submit your application. The said services provider is of the highest repute and verified by reliable security agencies like verisign etc. We use a service to convert your details uploaded within your online application to a PDF format. We also may use a third party address verification service and communication services for sending of SMS, Emails etc.

**IP Addresses**  
We may collect IP addresses. Your IP address is used to gather broad and specific demographic information as well as for validation purposes. In addition, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. (Please also see "Web Site Tracking Software," below.)

**Cookies**  
A "cookie" is a small text file that a website can place on your computer's hard drive in order to collect information about your activities on the website. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you have the option to change your browser settings to decline them. In order to use the Apply Online Program, you may need to enable cookies. We use cookies in order to verify your login credentials and to ensure that unauthorized users are not able to gain access to your application. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. (Please also see "Web Site Tracking Software," below.)

**Web Site Tracking Software**  
Web servers, or those of third-party vendors, utilize certain tracking software to capture your domain name address (the address of your Internet service provider) for purposes of tracking Website statistics. However, we do not capture any personally identifiable information in our website tracking software. The capture of your domain name is a common practice among websites for measuring the number of hits, pages visited, and length of user session. We use this information to measure the effectiveness of the Website offerings in order to service you better.

**Information Use**  
We are bound to transfer and share your information in full with the schools you apply for. By submitting your information to us and using our Website, you agree to allow us to transfer such data to such schools you apply for. Any other usage of your data would be done expressly with the permission of the school you have applied for in writing. We may also be bound to share the information given by you in the even t that the same is requested by a government agency or department in compliance with existing laws in our country.

**Security**  
Information we maintain about you is stored in a secure manner. We use security features to collect the information you provide to us via our Website in a secure manner. However, if you send us an email, that type of transmission of information is not secure, and is traveling though the Internet unprotected and can be intercepted. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or profile forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). While perfect security on the Internet is impossible, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the information you provide to us. We restrict access to this information to employees with a need to know this information to provide you with the benefit, assistance or service you request or would like to obtain, and to those employees that need the information to do their jobs.

**Minors**  
We adhere to all Indian government and specific state laws regarding visitors under 18 years of age. Any user who declares in the process to be under age 13 will not be allowed to register. Changes in UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the registration home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. The notice will tell you that we've changed our UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy and it will make available the prior UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy that applied (including, the dates that it applied). In addition, the updated UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy will list a new "Effective Date." If you continue to use our Website (as described above,i.e., when you: (1) access or use our Website or any of the webpages of our Website, (2) agree to receive e-mail from us and/or, (3) make application for a school through our Website), you are agreeing to be covered by the updated UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions or comments, please don't hesitate to contact us directly. We listen to and read every message sent to us, and we will endeavor to reply promptly to each one. Please email us with your questions or comments about this UCanApply.com Application Privacy Policy at admin@learningspiral.co.in, or you may call us at 033-40124111.

Our physical mailing address is,  
3A, Auckland Place, Room 5B, Floor 5th, Kolkatta-700017, West Bengal, India. 

We are an ISO 9001-2008 company and dedicated toward maintaining the best standards in service and technology.

__3A, Auckland Place, 5th Floor, Room 5B Kolkata – 700 017, West Bengal, India

Copyright © Learning Spiral Pvt. Ltd. 2016, All Rights Reserved.
